# **Erick Latshaw**

erickjlatshaw@gmail.com | Linkedin | Github | Portfolio

Junior Game Programmer

### **SUMMARY**

I am a passionate programmer and game developer with abilities in both 2D and 3D game creation. I have experience working in game jams as well as longer team projects. I am incredibly comfortable with version control and I pride myself in my clean code and game architecture with an emphasis on making designer-friendly, decoupled systems.

## **SKILLS**

Git Version Control, Unity, Unreal Engine, C#, C++

#### **PROJECT EXPERIENCE**

SEPTEMBER 2021 - DECEMBER 2021

Heavenly Sin, Unity, 13-person Team - 3D Dialogue-driven murder mystery/platforming game set in the 1920s

- Lead Programmer and manager of github throughout the entire project with no major loss of work
- Made and enforced a style guide as well as a github guide for team members
- Developed player controls, UI functionality, audio manager, settings manager, and save and load system
- Used scriptable objects as data containers, items, and events

OCTOBER 2021 - PRESENT

**Derpy Derby**, Unity, 2-person Team - *Online multiplayer party game where players control low-poly cars and smash into each other until there's a winner.* 

- Managed github
- Developed car controller, audio manager, car stats, networking, settings manager, server list

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

SEPTEMBER 2018 - MARCH 2020

Student Data Analyst, Marist College, Poughkeepsie, NY

- Gained real-world experience in data science
- Group project experience both virtual and in-person
- Regular use of MySQL, Python, and git
- Helped migrate databases from Netezza to MariaDB server

## **EDUCATION**

Expected May 2022

Marist College, Poughkeepsie, NY

BS, Games & Emerging Media - Technical Concentration